skipmcgrath.com 2019-03-14

# Auction Seller's Resource Privacy Policy

**Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties  
**We will never sell or give away your personal information to third parties for purposes of building contact lists, or anything of that nature, without your permission. 

Vision-One Marketing and The Auction Seller's Resource stands firmly against any transfer of personal information for reasons of building the contact lists of third parties. We do however, reserve the right to contact our customers to advise them of new product offerings and special rewards. This contact is very infrequent.

**Our monthly[newsletter subscriptions ](http://www.skipmcgrath.com/newsletters/)are administered by Aweber on a secure password-protected server and is only sent to confirm**ed subscribers who opt-in and then return a confirmation message.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Financial Information  
**We process all credit card transactions through PayPal and Verisign. Your financial information goes only to them. We have no access to your credit card information unless you telephone an order in and we process it directly through our merchant credit card account. 

If you paid by credit card and request a refund we will need to obtain your credit card number so we can credit back to the same card you purchased with.

**Information Automatically Logged**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. 

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

**Amazon Services LLC Associates Program**  
Harry McGrath, Inc., DBA Skip McGrath, Auction Seller's Resource and Vision-One Marketing is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.

**Policy Changes**  
We reserve the right to change our policy from time to time. A revised policy will apply to information collected after the date the policy is changed. 

**Effective Date**  
This policy is effective as of March 17, 2011.
